## Mohd Ariz Siddiqui

SRM Institute of Science and Technology, Kattankulathur, Tamil Nadu, India — IN 603203

M +91 8860896000

E <u>arizsiddiqui@hotmail.com</u>W <u>www.arizsiddiqui.tech</u>

L <u>arizsiddiqui</u>

Profile

A passionate third year computer science and engineering student with hands on experience in coding and software development. Presently leading a SRM Institute of Science and Technology National Level Tech fest (Aaruush) committee. A quick learner with strong communication and inter-personal skills, having successfully contributed to technical team success in projects with hard-work and attention-to-details. Additionally, cleared foundational level and now pursuing Diploma level skills in programming & Data Science from IIT Madras.

Experience

Microsoft Learn Student Ambassadors SRM - 2019-Present

Completed multiple projects under the banner of the Technical team of the club, including a NLP based browser extension, a CLI for keeping API and OAuth Tokens safe and a webinar on the basics of Python. Also, organised a hackathon, Resonate, with 500+ attendees.

Aaruush - 2019 - Present

Helped organise one of the largest techno-management fests in South India, playing a role in guest invitation and itinerary management. Personally tended to high-profile guests and successfully managed crisis situations.

Head Boy, Nirmal Bhartia School - 2018-2019

Served as the head of the Student Council of the school, helping implement regulations that improved the school life of the students.

Education

SRM Institute of Science and Technology, Kattankulathur, Tamil Nadu

Pursuing B.Tech. Computer Science and Engineering (3rd Year)

Technical Skills

Python, C, C++, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, Swift, SQL, Git, OpenCV, TensorFlow, Numpy, Pandas, Bootstrap, Scikit-learn, Scipy, Keras.

Soft Skills

Communication, Attention to detail, Quick learner, Delivers under pressure, Team worker.